<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>War Comes to Krynn on Dragonlance Player Resources</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in War Comes to Krynn on Dragonlance Player Resources</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Race Options</title>
      <link>https://example.org/character-creation/races/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/character-creation/races/</guid>
      <description>Race Options # Peoples of Krynn # The mysterious army threatens all the peoples of Krynn, driving them into the cities to seek shelter or help in the defense against this new threat.&#xA;Dwarves Dwarves # While known for their great subterranean nations, dwarves have long traded and traveled among the peoples of Krynn&amp;rsquo;s surface. The Cataclysm devastated many dwarven lands and destroyed some of their greatest underground kingdoms. Others, like the nation of Kayolin, were isolated from their allies as the New Sea flooded the land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Krynn</title>
      <link>https://example.org/history-of-krynn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/history-of-krynn/</guid>
      <description>A Brief History of Krynn # While every world&amp;rsquo;s history is vast and fractured, with missing pieces and forgotten perspectives, Krynn&amp;rsquo;s tale has been shattered by the global catastrophe called the Cataclysm. The world of Krynn was forged and destroyed, yet—broken and scarred—it continued on. Most of its people, seeking merely to survive in their slowly healing lands, care little for eons past. But the sages who piece together fragments of the past focus on three periods: before the Cataclysm, the Cataclysm itself, and the dire age since.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backgrounds</title>
      <link>https://example.org/character-creation/backgrounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/character-creation/backgrounds/</guid>
      <description>Backgrounds # This campaign introduces two unique backgrounds: Knight of Solamnia and Mage of High Sorcery. Be sure to check them out and see if you want to use one.&#xA;Disallowed Backgrounds # Most backgrounds can be made to work, even if they&amp;rsquo;re oddball ones. However, there are a few that are just too out of place to be worth trying to fit in here. These ones are disallowed, no negotiations:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feats</title>
      <link>https://example.org/character-creation/feats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/character-creation/feats/</guid>
      <description>Feats # This campaign grants a bonus feat for level 1 &amp;ndash; if you don&amp;rsquo;t choose a background that grants a feat, such as the Knight of Solamnia or Mage of High Sorcery backgrounds from this campaign &amp;ndash; and at level 4. All other prerequisites and feat rules apply.&#xA;Bonus Feats # 1st Level # If your background does not grant a feat, you may choose from the following feats at level 1:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/reference/</guid>
      <description>War Comes to Krynn # The world has ended, and it&amp;rsquo;s ending again.&#xA;Three hundred years ago, the Cataclysm brought ruin to the world of Krynn. In a single day, an age of wonders came to an end. Countless innocents died, the face of the world was reshaped, and the gods themselves faded into legend. Through ages of struggle, the peoples of Krynn survived, but the world isn&amp;rsquo;t what it was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>https://example.org/life-on-ansalon/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/life-on-ansalon/calendar/</guid>
      <description> Calendar # The lands around Kalaman use the Solamnic calendar, which has twelve months, each containing four weeks. Weeks have seven days, and days have twenty-four hours.&#xA;Solamnic Months # Month Name January Newkolt February Deepkolt March Brookgreen April Yurthgreen May Fleurgreen June Holmswelt July Fierswelt August Paleswelt September Reapember October Gildember November Darkember December Frostkolt Solamnic Days # Day Name Sunday Linaras Monday Palast Tuesday Magetag Wednesday Kirinor Thursday Misham Friday Bakukal Saturday Bracha </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Currency</title>
      <link>https://example.org/life-on-ansalon/currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/life-on-ansalon/currency/</guid>
      <description>Currency # Since the Cataclysm, the harsh realities of daily survival leave little room for impracticality. For years after the devastation, steel&amp;rsquo;s value skyrocketed until it was valued as highly as gold, thanks to the difficulty of forging steel and its obvious practical applications. Similarly, bronze was valued on par with silver. While the value of steel and bronze has diminished to pre-Cataclysm standards, trade coins of bronze and steel remain in use across Ansalon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Languages</title>
      <link>https://example.org/life-on-ansalon/languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/life-on-ansalon/languages/</guid>
      <description>Across Ansalon, language is an expression of upbringing and exposure. Before the Cataclysm, Common served as a language of commerce under the empires of Ergoth, Solamnia, and Istar. After the Cataclysm, migrating refugees communicated using Common, and today it&amp;rsquo;s spoken in every corner of the continent. Nevertheless, the local languages of most lands still flourish, and Common is used primarily in markets and in dealings with travelers.&#xA;A Note On Common: Unlike in some settings, where &amp;ldquo;Common&amp;rdquo; is an alias for a region&amp;rsquo;s most widely-spoken language, in Ansalon, Common is its own language, created from an amalgam of the other primary languages used in trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organizations</title>
      <link>https://example.org/life-on-ansalon/organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/life-on-ansalon/organizations/</guid>
      <description>Organizations # In eras past, when Krynn faced times of exceptional darkness, champions stepped forth from the ranks of the virtuous Knights of Solamnia and the mystical Mages of High Sorcery. These two organizations are detailed here.&#xA;Knights of Solamnia # Many celebrated heroes have risen from the Knights of Solamnia, the most storied knighthood on Ansalon. The knighthood began over a thousand years ago, during the reign of the Ergothian Empire in western Ansalon.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
